Guide to the Alfred and Hortense Wagenknecht and Helen and Carl Winter Family Papers TAM.583
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- II, Helen and Carl Winter Papers
  - V, Photographs
    - Leon Mosely Demonstration -- Detroit News Photos [Prints and Negatives], Jun 1948 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Mongolia, circa 1966 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Political Activities and Events [General], circa 1970-1999 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Romania, circa 1966 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Smith Act -- Miscellaneous, 1949-circa 1959 (Box 10, Folder 16)